Master, anyo haseyo!
So, I'm here for the first time overseas!
Not overseas, not overseas.
Año haseyo!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Shin-Okubo.
Oh, you're in Shin-Okubo?
Japanese is more common here, and it's still
That's why you didn't need a passport.
So that's how it is.
You can't go out on location.
And you and the master will enjoy yourselves.
We have guests from Harapeko!
Here they are!
Año haseyo!
A new channel is coming up!
Please give them our best regards. We are Shirute Bijutsu Gaku, attendance number 11, Kaho Kobayashi,
and Yuna Kokubo, attendance number 14. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Good morning.
Number 11 and 14.
Yes, number 11 and 14.
Good morning.
From the eternal junior high idols, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
Two people who have some connection to the show are here, and they're hungry.
Po-chan and...
And Yunopi.
Po-chan and Yunopi?
Yes, sir.
That's right.
You can call them that.
Po-chan is from Saitama Prefecture.What is it, Po, that you are from Saitama Prefecture?
Yes, I'm from the same family as you.
Well, not the same, but from the Asato world.
Same as Crayon Shin-chan, right?
That's right.
Can you do it, Crayon Shin-chan?
Nanako!
You can do it?
You're not bad!
There aren't many idols that can do it this well.
There's a lot of them.
I'm so embarrassed.
And Yunopi is from Aichi Prefecture.
Saitama.
That's right. I do this show in the Tokai area.
I see.
So you are from your hometown.
Thank you very much.
Then may I see Crayon Shin-chan?
Sure.
Nanako!
Do I look like her?
You look pretty good.
Let's see what we can do.
With these two... we'll be discussing oil.
I like oil, so I'm going to eat some Korean oil and make a shrimp face.
Yay!
It'll make everyone smile.
That's right, Korean food is popular among young people.
Inoculated in the Korean town Shin-OkuboLet's get inoculated in the Korean town Shin-Okubo and smile!
and get a smile on your face!
It's a great episode!
It's the best time!
Let's go to the first restaurant.
Let's go to the first restaurant!
The Harapeko Majin's Gourmet Magic: Oil Shoulder Bra!
Shin-Okubo, the holy land of Korean food!
Let's eat a lot of oil and get a smile on our Ebisu face!
Arrival
First stop, Korubok Shokudo!
Here we are!
I've never seen an opening this close to the restaurant!
It says "opening" on the menu!
It's an opening!
Opening time!
Basically, this is the place to shoot the opening!
Here we are at Koruboku Shokudo, a popular restaurant with a reputation for being the best in terms of cost performance in the Shin-Okubo area.
Korubok Shokudo, a popular restaurant with a long line!
I wonder what kind of kori oil they serve!
The kori oil served here is...
The oil menu has something to do with the two members of EBITU!
It's just like an arts and crafts world of oil!
The world of arts and sciences
What is the arts and crafts world?
It is unbelievable!
Ebichu is a junior high school, so the live concert is called "Gakugeikai" in the same way.
You mean live performance?
That's right!
It's common sense.It's common sense.
We're all in middle school.
For me, I'm in the 35th grade.
No, I'm a senior.
I'm part of the family.
I'm a family member.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are the fans of Ebitu?
We call our fans the Ebitu Family.
That's right.
We want you to know more about us.
I'm not sure if we have enough chili oil yet.
Let's taste it now!
KAZABURE-KAZABURE-KAZABURE-KAZABURE-KAZABURE
Yes! Title, title, title!
How's it coming?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
This is the specialty of the restaurant.
Shrimp roll samgyopsal.
Yay!
Looks delicious!
Oily pork belly wrapped around plump shrimp
Grilled until the surface is golden brown
Shrimp roll samgyeopsal is ready!
It's the beginning of the oil school arts and crafts festival!
I heard that there is a finishing touch.
Here is a little burner burner.
Burn it with a burner.
Where?
The shrimp?Shrimp?
Looks delicious.
Shrimp tails and crunchy.
It's pretty good.
I can taste it coming.
And the cheese has a nice char on it.
Wow!
Looks delicious!
And there's corn on the cob, too.
Is there a place where all the members of the Shrimp Club come together for dinner?
Between shows.
You said "live"!
The school arts festival.
You didn't say that.
I didn't!
I didn't say it!
I didn't say that.
No, you didn't.
I didn't.
The day after the school play, or when we're all having dinner together...
That's right.
But it's not that easy... because sometimes it's at Corona.
But nowadays, we usually go to live shows.
You said "live"!
No, we don't.
No, I haven't.
Go eat.
I didn't say that.
Okay, then. School lunch time.Okay, it's time for lunch.
Yay!
It's called school lunch.
School lunch!
Ready?
Bon appétit!
Here you go!
Pon-chan, you're growing so fast!
It stretches a lot.
Pon-chan!
How far should I go?
I can't cut it
You can't cut it!
Bon appétit!
It's hot, so be careful.
It's heavy.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
How do you like that?
Yum! Yum!
Yum!
It's so savory!
Oh, nice!
Shrimps are so soft and juicy!
Shrimp is so soft and juicy!
Delicious!Delicious!
Give me some Ebisugao, Ebisugao.
It's so cute!
It's good. It's good.
So cute.
Give me a yunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyunobiyu.
Bon appétit.
You're good at dipping.
It's delicious.
It's good. It's good.
It stretches.
You know what I'm talking about.
Stretch it, stretch it, stretch it.
Vienna.
They're connected.
Shrimp and hot water are connected.
Yummy.
Delicious!
Nice smile. Nice prawns.
Shibabi is good.
Shibaobi.
Shiba-bee
Shibabi.
Well, well, well, how is it?
Oh, it's good.
Very tasty.
Shrimp?
A really nice mixture of pork fat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Pretty fresh.Quite fresh
Yes, I'll take it.
Fresh.
It's like a first year of deliciousness.
Oh, it's delicious.
Delicious, isn't it?
Saltillas and, you know, even with a pinch, it's delicious.
I'd like to try a little bit.
Bon appétit!
Go ahead, go, go, go, go!
Wow!
Oh, it's totally different.
It's like eating a sandwich.
Like we're eating sandwiches.
It's like, "Well, why don't you just have a sandwich?
The tortillas are really good.
It's my first tortilla.
My first tortilla.
It's so good!
Yum!
What do you think?
It's so cute!
It's a little sticky, but it's got a different texture.
And the tortillas.
And the tortillas... the tortillas make the shrimp more juicy.
That's nice.
But you know what?
There's actually one more thing that I made with shrimp.
There's actually one more thing that we can do with shrimp.
So let's summon it!So let's summon them!
Abracadabra
Wow!
Here it comes!
It's in an ayuki state, isn't it?
This is amazing.
It's like shaved ice!
Snow Fee Shrimp!
Bite-sized shrimp with cheese.
Piled up like a mountain of snow
Our original menu!
Ladies and gentlemen, please wait!
We can't let you eat it for free.
That's great!
For the three of us.
A popular Korean TV drama.
Not the squid game.
Not the squid game, but the shrimp game.
The two winners will
winners will get a gourmet food!
And unfortunately
One who did not win
died.
Oh no.
While I was introducing myself
It's time to eat the food
Mr. Kobayashi, the winnerMr. Kobayashi, the Winner
Kunitomo-sama-sama
Please eat up!
Bo-chan Europie
Bo-chan Europie!
Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It stretches!
Amazing!
Bon appétit!
I can't get it off.
Boo hoo!
There's more family members.
Yum!
Delicious!
Asa Hi, I'd like to introduce myself, Bo-chan.
Yum!
The cheese is good.
It's different from the cheese we had earlier.
It's more creamy.
Bon appétit!
Careful with that.
Yum! There's corn in it.
There's corn in it? Here you go.
Yes, there's a little bit of corn.
Oh, wow.
The shrimp is so juicy and the corn is so crunchy.
Give me a good comment!
That was really good, you two.That was really good, you two.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong? I don't know.
I just couldn't get into it, I guess.
It's up to you. It's up to you.
Obracadabra.
Subscribe to our channel!